{
    "subject": "resource/Moloya_Goswami",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/India",
    "human_readable": "Moloya Goswami was born in India.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9110924601554871,
            "question": "Where was Moloya Goswami born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38774022459983826,
            "question": "Is there anything else you know about Moloya Goswami?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37130069732666016,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Moloya Goswami's background?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1692759096622467,
            "question": "What is India known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16098739206790924,
            "question": "What are some famous people from India?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14261680841445923,
            "question": "Who are some influential people from India?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11141049861907959,
            "question": "What is the culture like in India?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.08007502555847168,
            "question": "What are some interesting facts about India?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.07108267396688461,
            "question": "What is the history of India like?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.06257078051567078,
            "question": "What makes India a unique country?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Moloya Goswami was born in India.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8572_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the history of India like?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8572_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some interesting facts about India?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8572_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the culture like in India?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8572_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8572_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8572_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8572_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8572_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8572_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8572_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8572_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8572_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8572_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8572_62.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the required format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nExplanation:\nThe documents mention that Moloya Goswami was born and raised in Assam, a northeast state in India. This information indirectly implies that she was indeed born in India."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Moloya Goswami is from Assam, a northeastern state of India. Therefore, the statement \"Moloya Goswami was born in India\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}